Prozorov Mykhailo

26 April 1990 Kyiv myhajlo.prozorov@gmail.com



.NET Developer

Summary

For the last three years I have been working with high-load systems. Current working system handles 15M request per day. I have increased speed of internal program in 60 times (I reduced CPU working time, and I made parallel execution of async processes). Now it works less than 10 min. Before some of jobs had executed during 6 hours every time. Systems stability by number of exceptions was improved. I did intergation with different systems such as Esputnik or Amazon SES.

I have created new .Net Core services. Also I moved some internal services into .Net Core where it was needed.

Our team have been developing inner CRM for 6 mounth from scratch. CRM has already runs and our sales managers use it. We used GraphQL as single HTTP API. It consumes a lot of events from Kafka and handles it. We used Elasticsearch for storing.

I have skils to find bottlenecks performance and fix them. I can analize memory dump, use different profilers to search reasons of performance decreasing.

I was writting code on C# the most time. I was full stack developer some times. But I have closed the most tasks on Back-end side.

I did SQL queries by different ORM: Dapper, NHibernate, EF.

I have been writting 90% of code on .NET Core during last 18 mounths with using Kubernetes, Kafka, ElasticSearch, GraphQL.

I have small experience/knowledge in:

- Redis, MongoDB,
- Selenium
- JavaScript, Bootstrap, Angular
- Git

Work experience

.NET developer

August 2020 – Currently **NewGround**

C#/.NET Mentor

September 2020 - Currently

FoxmindEd

Education Company

Back-end developer

March 2019 – May 2020 (1 year 5 mounths) **robota.ua**

Job search site

Back-end developer

October 2018 - February 2019 (3 mounths)

Homsters

Real estate advertise site

.NET developer

April 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 8 mounths) **Moneyveo**

Payday loans by online

Back-end developer

April 2013 - April 2017 (4 years 1 mounths)
Other small IT companies

Education

National Aviation University (Kyiv)

2007-2013

Computer Science

Languages

English - A2

I can be interviewed